Guys, actually I just remembered I was a
190 lbs before giving birth. I'm
curious. So, we're going to go see like
how much I weigh in. Guys, we're doing a
mini mommy makeover [music] today. I
haven't dyed my hair since November of
2024.
Keeping myself alive is very hard. Like,
hello friends. What's up? We are
preparing for a little mini barbecue.
My dad's going to barbecue. So, I'm
going to just wait outside.
Come on, Cheddar. You want to come? No.
Okay.
Papa, you need help?
I'll sit. I'll be in the shade here.
Almost ready. Everything.
>> It's nice out. last few
weeks.
Oh, you broke them.
That's funny. It is the next day, guys.
I have my one of my childhood friends or
middle school friends coming to see us
with her mom. So, mom just hyper cleaned
the entire house like a superwoman.
And I just remembered I have to take, if
you guys ever tried pure cranberry
juice, it tastes nothing like the
cocktail, it is the most sour juice I've
ever had in my life. But I am dealing
with a serious infection of like, you
know, where they put the catheter and it
is really, really painful. So, in the
meantime, in the meantime, while I'm
getting my urine tested and all that,
she told me to have pure cranberry
juice, which I'm only going to have this
much at a time, and also take cranberry
pills. So, that's what I've been doing,
but
it is so sour. We're also going to get
my blood levels checked, I think, in a
few days because I don't know if you
guys can tell, but my eye bags and my
lips are eye bags are dark, lips are
pale. So, they want to see if Where is
my cranberry pills? Oh, here they are.
They want to see if or whatever. I need
another infusion. So, most likely that
will happen in the next week or so. But
other than that, we are feeling okay.
Oh my god.
Also, Osami and Sana got me these drops.
Let me know if you guys have tried them.
Let me show you them first. There's two
different ones. It is the Rumina
Goats Rue and Rumina the Milky Way. And
they're both herbal tinctures. And they
both help with milk supply. But you
guys, every time I drink it, you're
supposed to mix it in something. The
first time I mixed it, I mixed it in
water cuz Santa's like, "Just put in a
little bit of water and drink it." I
gagged. I almost threw up. So, even in
this really, really sour juice, I've
been putting these and I still gag every
single time. So, I don't know. But,
we're going to we're going to take it.
But if you guys have ever had this and
there's anything that can mask the taste
of this, please let me know cuz you're
supposed to have this three times a day
and I'm currently only having it once a
day.
We'll give him his drops, mama. So, all
right, fine. I won't traumatize him
right now. [sighs]
I'm going to vomit. I need to have water
with it. I know. I felt feel bad. He's
just looking at us with his puppy dog
eyes. Poor guy. I told him we're just
learning the new schedule and then he'll
get love. Vada. I know.
>> Like a toy.
>> Poor guy.
>> You guys didn't sleep.
>> Nobody in this house is getting any good
sleep. That's why you guys should get
some rest. Okay, let's see. Guys, I
ordered a playmat
for tummy time.
One of these like colorful situations.
See,
that way he has something to play on.
Will it need a battery?
Baby Einstein.
There was like a black and white one.
And I ended up getting the colorful one
just cuz I'll get more use out of it.
Okay. We're going to have to build this.
Okay.
All right. All right.
And what? This runs on batteries, I
guess. Okay. Yeah. I'm just going to
quickly make this
>> [music]
>> ta.
It's done. I got to just put in the
batteries now.
>> This is something new.
>> That is a chi. It was really good.
>> My friend here brought these cookies. Oh
my god. So yummy. M's mom sent me so
much food
>> home. The soup is so good. Especially
cuz I haven't been
>> Yeah.
>> Especially cuz I haven't been
feeling like eating. Even though they
say you're supposed to be really hungry
when you're breastfeeding, I just
haven't been. So, my miss.
Good morning. I washed my hair last
night and I half blow dried it and then
I gave up. So, we're going to quickly
straighten this hair before the baby
wakes up and before I have to feed him.
So, with the magic of editing, we're
going to go from this to straight hair.
And now,
taa. Okay, now let's go feed the baby
and then we'll continue the rest of the
day. Guys, actually I just remembered I
was a 190 lb before giving birth. I'm
curious. So, we're going to go see like
how much I weigh in it. Just out of
curiosity. I'm a little out of breath.
So, this is what we're working with.
My belly is still like, you know, jello.
It's healing. Hold on. I want to say
just like a few days after I gave birth,
I restarted doing it. And it is the 360
breathing. if you guys haven't ever done
it or you don't have to do it while
you're pregnant even, but it helps a lot
with your core and just keeping
everything steady. So, we're not really
working like for abs, but we're working
on the pelvic floor, your ab like just
your core internally. And basically what
you do, it's going to be hard to see,
but you're going to go, you breathe
completely in, fill in your belly, and
then as you're breathing out, suck in
your stomach, but you're going to try to
like envision your belly button being
pulled back. So you go.
[sighs and gasps] So breathe in
like that. Should go kind of like pull
everything out. And then breathe in
again and fill in your stomach. And it
helps keeping your hands here to help
fill out your stomach because you want
to completely relax those muscles before
pushing them back in. And I do this
whenever I like can think of, especially
when I'm in the shower, if I'm just here
like in the bathroom. It helps a lot. I
have my weighing machine right here.
We are
167bs. So, I was like 192 before I gave
birth. And even the 192, it was like
maybe a week before I gave birth. Those
last few days of like before I gave
birth, oh my god, I was like swelling up
like a balloon. So, it might have even
been over 192. But 192US
167, it's about 25 lb that I have lost
just in having the baby, swelling,
fluids, and all of the extra stuff. So,
which is not bad. We are 167. My weight
before giving birth was 144. So, before
I even got pregnant, I was already
trying to not gain weight, but I was
trying not actively lose weight because
I was trying to get pregnant. So, I had
already gained from like 135 to 144,
like a solid 8 to 10 lbs in the 3 months
leading up to when I got pregnant
because like I didn't want to put my
body in stress. I wanted it to have like
good food, nutrients, blah blah blah
blah. So, I now just I'll be happy at
like 145, you know what I mean? So,
another it would be another 20 lbs. Am I
dumb? But I still have four more weeks
of proper healing. So, I'm definitely
going to take advantage of that. I I'm
going to start going for walks because
you guys are going to die at my step
count. Oh my god. I don't know if you
can see, but it's all red. Like today,
it's only tracked 345 steps, which my
phone is down and I'm not moving around
that much, but
yikes.
We'll see.
Okay guys, we're doing a mini mommy
makeover today. So, take a good look at
this hair. I haven't dyed my hair since
November of 2024. Like when we went to
Pakistan, the entire family. And since
then, that's why you guys see a lot of
like white hair in my hair as well. So,
take a good look at this hair. But I'm
here at Senna's mom's salon. If you guys
don't know, I'm going to tag her
Instagram here. She's genuinely after so
many years of brands and paid things
ruining my hair. She's genuinely the
only one that I trust on starting this
hair journey, but like very slowly. So,
what we're going to try to do is just
add some what are they called? Low
lights. Like just a little bit of
lightness here. Maybe lighten the bangs
a little bit. And then maybe in 2 months
I'll come back and then we'll start the
lightening process. I don't want to be
like a bleach blonde or anything like
that. But I just want I don't know,
something new and fresh. Like I said,
and Addios knows how to do it really
well. So, I don't think I'm not going to
do a haircut cuz you guys know I just
recently got a haircut, but I'm really
excited. So, let's do this.
Oh my god. It's literally exactly what I
asked for. just like something subtle.
I'm going to put makeup on and do like
the final look. Mass is here to pick me
up. So, I'll talk to you guys at home.
Guys, we stopped at Shoppers and look
what I found. I'm in my pantry right
now. Okay. And I thought cuz usually
Canada doesn't get all the new releases,
especially like food stuff. But look
what I found. It is KD ramen. So, I got
all three flavors. So, I got extra
cheesy. I got extra spicy. And this one
is just plain cheesy. And we already
know I'm going to try the extra spicy.
And I'm really excited. So, yeah. I'm so
[snorts] excited cuz if it's I like
regular KD, you know me, I'm just like a
not I don't know if you guys know me,
but sometimes you just want girl dinner
and a basic craft dinner is just what I
want. So, how do we make this? Probably
the regular
instructions.
Open here for instructions.
Tada. Let's see. Remove the lid. Add
water and microwave.
Stir in the cheese and seasoning.
All right.
Pretty easy. Let's have it. Especially
cuz Massu is not home and he doesn't
need to know that I'm having just Katie
for dinner because he wants me to always
have more protein. I'm just not in the
mood for protein these days. Okay.
Remove lid fully pouches.
Okay. Just looks like the plain ramen
noodles.
And where are we going to fill it until?
Do not
fill over the line. What is the fill
line? I'm confused.
Okay, it's fine. My mom's watching Baby
Reindeer.
Okay, I think that's good. I think
that's the fill line. And now we're
going to put it in for 4 minutes.
Actually, we'll do 3 and 1/2 minutes
because times vary.
Yeah.
3 minutes 30 seconds start
right and then we just mix in the cheese
seasonings and we're done. I should have
made this on the stove cuz I usually
make regular KD on the stove but it's
fine. We're going to just try the way
that it's meant to be. These are the
little packets. I think this is like the
spice and this is the cheese. Okay, I'm
going to pair this with a mango juice.
If there's a better mango juice than
this, let me know. But that one is my
favorite.
Okay,
it is hot.
All right, let's add in our seasonings.
Oh yeah.
I mean, it definitely looks better on
the packet, but we'll see.
Okay. It's a little hard to mix.
touch.
>> Yeah. 6 out of 10. I wouldn't get it
again. Actually, I take that rating back
in our house or especially me and my
younger brother, we rate things either a
zero or a one, which means zero being
you wouldn't go to this restaurant again
or you would have it again and one being
you would. Does that make sense? And
zero, I'm going to rate this zero cuz I
would not have it again cuz Yeah. So,
no. Good morning. We're going to make
Turkish eggs today for breakfast.
So, I got to just take out everything.
Okay. Water on boil.
Okay.
Okay. Bring your water to a boil. And
now the yogurt.
Going to finally chop up like half a
clove.
Chop up the garlic as finely as you can.
Put in the garlic.
Some dill.
Mix that in.
Salt,
pepper
there.
That's our base. Now we just make the
eggs. Okay.
Wait for it to come to like we're
[clears throat] going to do poached
[music] eggs. So, a rolling boil, but
then you got to bring it back down so
it's not hardcore rolling. [music]
And then in another pan, we're going to
melt butter with some tomatoes and a
little bit of chili flakes. And you're
going to need
a sifter like this.
Okay. Little bit of butter.
Little bit of oil.
Let that melt.
And then I'm just going to chop up some
tomatoes and put them in there to get
like blistered. And now the water. I'm
going to
bring it to back down to like a simmer,
not like a crazy boil. And then we're
[music] going to start our eggs. So,
we're going to do two eggs at a time.
And you want to sift it
because that watery part [music] of the
egg is going to make your water for the
poached eggs all like streaky and runny.
[music]
So, just sift it into here.
And once it's all gone through, just
transfer it to another another bowl.
That's one.
And
[clears throat]
okay, I'm going to wait for these to get
blistered up.
I'm also going to put in my chili
flakes.
Okay,
before I cook the eggs, I always place
the yogurt
on it, the plate, because as soon as the
eggs are cooked, you just transfer it on
here.
See?
Okay, let's make these poached eggs.
This is the hard part.
You're going to make a swirl.
I haven't done this in like 9 months, so
they might go bad, but we'll see.
Swirl
and drop.
Another swirl
Very good.
And keep swirling.
Okay, it only takes about like almost 2
minutes. You don't want them to get
obviously too hard.
I don't know how to make sure that
they're done, but I can see like the
whites are still a little jiggly.
So,
like this one
could possibly be done. Oh no, I broke
it.
I'll just hold it here. Okay. And what I
like to do is I like to break the yolk
like this.
Okay. And then
put on all of this tomato sauce.
There we go.
That is my breakfast.
Now I'm just going to make it one more
time for my mom and my sud.
Have some chai. And that's it. All
right, guys. You guys already know the
drill. You don't know if you truly love
your new hair until you do your makeup.
So, I am going to do my makeup
quickly. I do already love it though.
It's actually like exactly the inspo
photos I wanted, but I do want to see
how it looks with makeup on, too.
Quickly do my eyebrows. I usually mix
these two together, but today, because
I'm in a rush, I'm only going to do the
L'Oreal one.
Also, while I'm here, I just wanted to
say a quick thank you to every single
one of you that has shown love and
support for my birth story. And
honestly, reading everybody's comments,
I've learned so much with the condition
or whatever happened to me, I learned
more through the comment section than I
was basically told at the hospital. So,
now I feel like I have a good idea of
like when my next appointment is or my
next checkup is. I have a good idea of
like everything I want to ask them in
terms of like what happened with me and
stuff. I'm also I'm going to try my best
to not talk about this so often and make
just every single video about obviously
the goal is to heal and move forward. So
I will just give you guys updates here
and there on anything new I figure out
what with what's going on. But I also
know that not everybody wants to hear
about this all the time. So, we will
also try to go back to regular content
and you know, I can raise awareness here
and there about what happened with me
just so any other pregnant women can
maybe if you feel like what happened to
me is the issue that you're going to
have, you can just get it checked from
your doctor. You know what I mean? So,
if you've been watching my last few
videos, my favorite thing to do right
now is like basically like a reverse
makeup tutorial, which is I start with
contour, then I do my blush, and then I
do my concealer and foundation. And I
feel like if you're going for like an
everyday makeup look, it just helps not
make everything look so heavy. And it's
really fast. So, normally I use my
Makeup Forever skin tint. This I love so
much because it's an actual skin tint.
So many skin tints out there in the
market. it might as well just be
marketed as like a full coverage
foundation. You know what I mean? But
this one, it just gives you a little bit
of coverage. But today, I'm going to use
something with more coverage.
What else, guys? I these lashes lasted
me so long, but I don't know if I've
asked you already, but if you have any
recommendations on lash cluster glues
that you love and that last a long time,
please let me know. Cuz currently I'm
just using this one that I got on
Amazon. It's okay, but I know that
there's probably like a much better one
out there. And I have been enjoying
having these lashes on because I'm just
not putting on makeup every single day.
Um, so it just makes sense
for me to have the lashes on. I just
feel a little better, you know, like
more like myself. I did my own lash
clusters and that's what I've been doing
like since I got home from the hospital
cuz it's so convenient and easy and I'm
not wearing makeup on a daily basis.
That concealer is too light. I am
literally
I'm literally so nervous for postpartum.
I know I'm [snorts] still like
only 3 weeks, but how my body and mind
is going to react to it. So, I've been
trying to like as much as I can like get
some fresh air whenever I'm able to. But
obviously, I'm still really healing from
all of the trauma, so I can't push
myself that much. But I'll tell you guys
when my hair starts falling out. I am
still taking my prenatal vitamins
because everybody says like continue
taking your vitamins because especially
if you're like breastfeeding, you're
going to be losing a lot of nutrients in
your system. But also, I don't think I'm
having like I don't think I'm like
giving myself enough nutrients. I'll be
honest. I I haven't been feeling hungry
even though everyone says like when
you're breastfeeding you feel so hungry
all the time. And I almost feel like I
have to force myself to eat. So, I don't
know if that's going to change. And I
just Yeah, I I just know I'm not giving
myself enough nutrients. I just know it.
So, I'm trying to figure out like how to
do this. I don't know. There's just so
much on my plate. Like, you have to keep
your baby alive and then you got to also
try to keep yourself alive. And
keeping myself alive is very hard. Like,
I don't know what to feed myself. And
it's just like, you know, when you have
decision fatigue, it's just like so much
that I have to I feel like on my mind
already that
the last thing I want to focus on is
myself, which isn't good. I know you're
supposed to focus on yourself more
because if you're healthy and happy,
everyone around you is healthy and
happy. You know what I'm saying?
Especially if you're the mom, but
I'm also It's still pretty fresh. Cute.
I think that's good. I don't want to do
like anything too crazy for lips. We're
just going to do I have so much new
makeup, guys, that I should be trying,
but it's all in that box behind me and
just taking it out is like stressful for
me for some reason. Like I said,
decision fatigue or whatever it is.
Um, so I just don't even bother.
Where is my sharpener?
Here
it is. Lips. We're just going to do my
usual Makeup Forever Makeup Talk
and YSL lip blusher in number 44. It's
literally the prettiest pink combination
ever.
Okay, we're going to keep it at this.
Now, I'm just going to fix my hair a
little bit because I did sleep in it. I
got this done yesterday, so we'll fix it
up.
Where does this hair go?
Okay, there you go.
I don't know if I'm going to Maybe I
should just take like a round brush.
What should I do?
Right. Maybe I'll take like a round
brush and just
I don't know. Oh, should I do a round
brush or like a straightener?
I don't know what to do. Okay, let's do
a round brush. Okay.
No, guys. I don't know how to do my hair
anymore. What's wrong with me? You know
what? I don't care. I'm too lazy. I
don't want to do my hair right now. I
think that's fine, right? How? I think
it looks good. I already knew I like the
hair, but I mean with makeup, we know we
like it even more. So, I'm going to end
the vlog here cuz at this point, we've
been going for 10 days. I don't even
know what I filmed anymore. So, that
means it's my cue to end it here and
pick back up on the next one. Bye.